Adam Field Overview



I have spent the past two years studying web development at SAE in London. This course covered a range of web languages as well as human computer interaction, localisation and accessibility. For my dissertation I am investigating how embedded systems can be used to monitor and control a food production system.

I am due to complete the course at the end of August and will be looking for full time employment. I would like to use the knowledge I have learned over the past two years, combined with my non-technical skills, in a role geared towards project management.

Contact Details



07590 472355



www.afield.io



adam@afield.io



HCI

JAVA

in/amfield1

Employment

Student Supervisor

Jan 2014 - Current

Supervised PHP Lab sessions and tutorials for the students in the junior year.

Labourer

Mar 2012 - Sep 2012

Hands on work with a small team of builders. This involved various skills including electrics, plumbing and carpentry.

Commercial Pilot

Nov 2007 - Dec 2011

I was a Senior First officer for Ryanair responsible for the safety of passengers and crew whilst ensuring a timely and efficient operation.

Education

Technical Skills

SAE Web Development

Sep 2012 - Current

HTML/CSS/JS/AS/PHP/Symfony2/JAVA/Android/Libgdx/Sketch/Python Accessibility/Localisation/Human Computer Interaction/ Design.

HTML/CSS **JavaScript** PHP

Open University

Oct 2011 - Mar 2012

Personal development with the Open University. 75% in Design and Designing. Focused on the product life cycle and sustainability.

Oxford Aviation Training

Sep 2005 - Sep 2007

Averaged 91% across 15 ground school modules in 6 months. First time pass in CPL(IR) ME (Final Flight Test)

Non-Technical Skills

Interests and Achievements

Leadership Communication Time Management

Public Speaking

Situational Awareness

Currently working on a side project called FishFish. www.fishfishapp.com

Avid reader of Wired Magazine and new found fascination with Aguaponic Farming. Lover of the Cinema and a good TV series. Handy with a drill, saw and power tools.

Completed the 2012 London Marathon in 4hrs 11mins and have my PADI Divemaster Certificate.

Please feel free to get in touch. I look forward to hearing from you.